

BIO

My name is Colton and I'm a 24-yearold full-stack web and app developer living in Raleigh, NC. I'm currently enrolled at Wake Tech Community College for an AAS in Web Development, finishing up in Spring 2022. I take an interest in building modern interfaces and experiences with technologies such as React/Vue, Express, MongoDB, and more!

I consider myself a highly-motivated individual – both at work and at home. I'm frequently challenging myself with new projects and learning new technologies. My skills range far beyond web development though, with hobby work done in music and video development, game development, and more extensively graphic design.

CONTACT

PHONE: 919-885-6327

WEBSITE:

www.coltonsweeney.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/coltonsweeney/ www.github.com/coltoncs

EMAIL:

Colton.sweeney@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Hiking/Physical fitness Hobby web & app projects Game development **Automotives**

COLTON **SWEENEY**

Full-Stack Web Developer

EDUCATION

Wake Technical Community College

2020 - 2022

Completing Associate of Applied Science for Web Development, along with a series of certificates. Courses include:

- Web and Mobile Design
- Network and Security Foundations
- Data-Driven Websites & ASP.NET
- Advanced Markup and Scripting

Apex High School

2012 - 2016

Enrolled in classes such as SAS Programming, Graphic Design, C# Programming, and Java Programming. Earned the Adobe Certified Expert - Adobe Photoshop 2015.

WORK EXPERIENCE

United Restaurant Equipment Company – Web Developer January 2021-Present

- Working on redesigning and redeveloping e-commerce platform on BigCommerce and NetSuite.
- Increased online revenue +170% YTD, orders by +75% YTD
- Increased conversion rate by +82% YTD
- Implemented domain change and setup Google Analytics

Progress Software - Product Marketing Intern

July 2016-Dec 2020

- Built a cross-platform mobile application for the sales teams to receive customer and product data quickly and with ease.
- Published multiple product content pieces, such as infographics, whitepapers, blog posts, and technical how-to tutorials (available on my LinkedIn).
- Created Alexa bots for showcasing products at partner events.

TECHNICAL EXPERIENCE

HTML/CSS/JS TailwindCSS, Bulma, Bootstrap ExpressJS, NextJS. MeteorJS ReactJS, VueJS Visual Studio, VSCode, Eclipse MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL AWS Amplify, EC2, S3, Lambda Netlify/Heroku/Firebase Linux, Windows, MacOS **Certified Adobe CC Suite** Go, Python, Node Backends C#, C++, .NET